居然有人要在餐厅求婚
Got a marriage proposal in the diner.
他们要去哪里蜜月呢 "屎"多黎各吗
Where they gonna honeymoon-- a Porta-Potty?
这是我见过最悲哀的事情了
That's the saddest thing I ever seen,
比昨晚的滚石老人乐队演唱会还凄惨
and I was at a Rolling Stones concert last night.
那男主想我把戒指放到女主的派里
The guy wants me to put this ring her pie.
毕竟有一首歌唱到
'Cause you know what they say--
喜欢它[她] 就给戴上[放进]戒指
If you like it, then you gotta put a ring in it.
这也算是头一遭
Well, this is a first.
有个男的用吃剩的半个三明治付小费
A guy left me a half a tuna sandwich as a tip.
不过这也比穷光蛋欧洲人给的多了
Which is still more than Europeans leave.
四十号桌要求婚
There's a proposal at table 40,
这个任务得你来做
and you have to do it.
我今天已经在餐厅里接生过婴儿了
I already delivered a baby in here today.
看来他们已经好了一段时间了
Well, they've obviously been dating a while,
这妞都敢在他面前吃会胖的东西了
'cause she's eating carbs in front of him.
卡洛琳现在超开心
Caroline is so happy right now.
她还相信那些狗屁爱情玩意
She still believes in all that love crap.
她也相信十四号桌是四十号桌
Uh, she also believes table 14 is table 40.
这是您的派
Here's your pie.
我感觉这盘甜点一定会特别"甜"呢
I have a feeling this dessert is gonna be extra-sweet.
这是订婚戒指
It's an engagement ring!
是他藏在派里的
He hid it in the pie!
好 愿意 我愿意嫁给你
Yes! Yes, I'll marry you.
我知道我之前说我不介意等
I know I said I was cool with waiting,
但其实我很介意
but I wasn't cool with it!
她弄错了 这不是你的戒指
Yep. She messed up. This isn't yours.
再说一次 我真的不介意等
Um...again. I'm cool with waiting.
至于你们俩呢 这派免费
And for you two, pie on the house,
我猜回家的出租车上会尴尬死
and I'm guessing a very tense cab ride home.
厄尔上哪了 现在都还没到
Where's Earl? He isn't here yet,
我好担心他
and I'm worried.
等等 今天不是什么黑人假日吧
Wait--it's not a black holiday, is it?
厄尔最好不是死了 不然我一定杀了他
Earl better not be dead, or I'll kill him.
我们有一个大麻自杀协议
We have a joint suicide pact.
我们一起抽一管大麻 然后自杀
We smoke a joint and then we kill ourselves.
他可能只是迟到而已 不用反应过度
He's probably just late. Don't overreact.
我十分钟前打给911 跟接线小姐抓狂
That's exactly what Janine at 911 said ten minutes ago
她也说了你说的话
when I overreacted with her!
你居然打给911了
You called 911?
我昨晚晚回家三个小时而已
When I came home three hours late last night,
你就已经把我所有的东西都搬到街上去了
you had already put all my stuff out on the street.
大家安安
Hi, everybody!
等等 厄尔人呢
Wait a minute-- where's Earl?
少了他坐下面看我巨乳
It's not as much fun walking in here
我进店里的乐趣就少了好多啊
if he's not down there looking up at my boobs.
他迟到
He's late.
"迟到"吗
Late?
节哀 麦克斯
Oh...I'm sorry, Max.
我知道你们情同父女
I know you two were close.
看到没 我跟你还有接线员说这事的时候
See? That's the kind of sympathy I was looking for
想要的就是这种同情慰问
from you and Janine.
苏菲 这一大堆针是干嘛的
Sophie, what's with those needles?
准备拿来打针用的
Oh, yeah--I'm getting ready to shoot up.
苏菲今天要开始打排卵针
Sophie's starting her fertility shots today.
不久之后 我们就能为人父母了
Before long, we'll be parents.
小心了 未来的PTA[家长会]
Look out, PTA meetings...
我负责带P[阴茎] 她负责带TA[奶+臀]
I'll bring the P. She'll bring the T&A.
来吧 奥列格 我准备好打第一针了
All right, come on, Oleg. I'm ready for my first shot.
走吧 咱们去女厕
Come on, let's go to the ladies' room
这样你能好好"捅"我一针
so you can poke me real good.
你不准在餐厅里任何地方"捅"她
You're not poking her anywhere in here.
多谢你们 现在残疾人厕所成了套套乱葬岗
Thanks to you, the handicap stall is a condom graveyard!
苏菲 我这辈子只怕两样东西
Sophie, you know I'm only afraid of two things--
针头与眼睑拉皮后的歌手肯尼·罗杰斯
needles and Kenny Rogers after the eyelift.
他不知道什么时候该折起眼皮
He did not know when to fold 'em.
得找别人帮你打这个针
Someone else will have to give you your shots.
我可以帮忙
Well, I guess I could do it.
把袖子卷起来吧
Roll up your sleeve.
好吧 行
Okay, yeah.
我就卷起我的袖子
I'll roll up my sleeve...
再脱下我的塑身裤
and then pull down my Spanx,
你得把针扎到我那"阳光不闪耀之处"
'cause you gotta put it where the sun don't shine, baby.
这有点尴尬啊 苏菲
Uh...this is a little awkward, but Sophie,
我原先真不知道得帮你在丰臀扎针
I was unaware I'd be injecting your badonkadonk.
好了 阿憨
Okay, Han.
牵我的手
Take my hand...
没错
That's right.
这就对了 来吧
That's real good. All right, come on.
我现在要带你去
And I'm gonna take you now
见识你人生第一个女人屁股
to show you your first lady butt.
这如此温暖有爱的一幕
Now, there's a heart-warming tableau
插画家洛克威尔不知怎么地错过了啊
that Norman Rockwell somehow missed.
姑娘们晚上好
Hello, ladies.
厄尔 你还活着我好庆幸
Earl! I'm so glad you're alive.
麦克斯 你每次总是直接想到我挂了
You always go straight to dead, Max.
不过还是谢谢你帮我叫了医务人员
But thanks for sending the paramedics.
我的确需要有人来帮我找苹果电视盒遥控
I needed help finding my Apple TV remote.
我跟巴里电话说太久
I was stuck on the phone with Barry
他是我以前"早鸟"爵士乐队的伙伴
from my old jazz band The Early Birds.
你在《从未闯出名堂》杂志上可能看过我们
You may have read about us in "Never Made It" magazine.
我跟卡洛琳还是上周的封面人物呢
Caroline and I were on the cover last week.
他跟我说露比爵士酒吧要办周年纪念演出
He told me they are holding a anniversary show down at Ruby's,
而这周五晚我们早鸟乐队
and The Early Birds are invited to perform
被邀请去演出
on Friday night.
厄尔
Earl!
我其中一个梦想就是看你现场演出
One of my dreams is to hear you play live.
而另一个梦想已经实现了
And the other one already happened--
麦当劳早餐全天都卖
breakfast all day at McDonald's.
麦克斯 我不想戳破你麦满分般的幻想
Well, I hate to burst your McMuffin, Max,
但你的梦想不会实现了
but that ain't gonna happen,
因为我没被邀请去演出
'cause I'm not invited to play.
露比不想看到我
Ruby doesn't want me there.
露比恨厄尔
Ruby hates Earl.
那麦克斯就恨露比
Well, then Max hates Ruby.
你跟露比之间是发生了什么呀
Oh! What happened between you and Ruby?
一场疯狂的风流韵事吗
Was it a crazy love affair?
的确是十分热辣
We were hot.
"疯狂的爱"吗[法语]
Oh! An amour fou?
不 是我跟人家妹妹"疯狂爱爱"了
No, it was a-more I fooled around with her sister.
看 厄尔与早鸟乐队的唱片
Look! Earl and The Early Birds!
你从哪弄来的
Where'd you get that?
我去唱片店买的
I went down the street to Smart & Vinyl.
你花12.95块买厄尔的唱片
You spent 12.95 on Earl's record,
可是昨天我买咖啡差2毛5你却不借我钱
but you wouldn't lend me 25 cents for a latte yesterday?
我们必须得想办法帮帮厄尔
Look, we gotta do something about Earl.
在那爵士酒吧表演的机会是他应得的
He deserves to play at that jazz club.
他可是我们这餐厅里
I mean, he is the only one at this diner
最有机会闯出名堂的人了
who has a chance to make it.
我很欣赏你的热情 但餐厅的所有人中
I appreciate your enthusiasm, but of all of us here,
你觉得是这位80岁老人的未来最光明吗
you think the 80-year-old has the brightest future?
从我一开始认识厄尔到现在
For as long as I've known Earl,
他嘴上总是挂着他有多为那乐团骄傲
all he talked about is how proud he was of that band.
而这个就叫露比的女人
And that Ruby woman
居然想要阻挡他再次演出的机会
is denying him the chance to play again?
有我在[手表] 就不可能
Not on my watch.
如果我有一只
If I own one.
不过... 我没有
Which...I do not.
我们得去那家酒吧
We are going down to that club
跟露比讲讲道理
and talk some sense into Ruby,
如果我们有点才华 厄尔也会为我们出头
because Earl would do the same for us if we had any talent.
我不得不问
I just have to ask--
你真心觉得我们有天能离开这里的吧
you do think we're gonna get out of here one day.
当然啊
Oh, for sure!
在装尸袋里被送出去
In body bags.
这地方真像那么回事
Wow, this place is the real deal!
很多爵士大家都在这里唱过
All the jazz greats sang here.
艾拉·费兹洁拉 萨拉·沃恩 妮娜·西蒙
Look--Ella Fitzgerald, Sarah Vaughan, Nina Simone.
你知道曾经有段时间我也想...
You know, there was a moment when I wanted to be--
你有过任何时间是你想安静闭嘴的吗
Was there ever a moment when you wanted to be quiet?
麻烦来杯免费的威士忌
Scotch on the house, please.
我通常下午不喝酒
Normally, I don't drink in the afternoon,
但现在还是早上
but it's still morning.
我要杯利莱酒
I'll have a Lillet.
我听说比莉·荷莉戴[歌手]就爱喝这个
I hear it was Billie Holiday's poison.
曾有过一段时间我...
You know, there was a moment when I was--
那段时间已经过去了
That moment's over.
先生 我们来找露比
Sir, we're here to see Ruby.
谁想见露比
Who wants to see Ruby?
麦克斯 她来势汹汹啊
She's coming in real hot, Max.
来找她可能不是好主意
Maybe this isn't a good idea.
世界上唯一让我害怕的老女人只有一个
There's only one old woman who scares me,
他的名字叫史蒂芬·泰勒
and his name is Steven Tyler.
我就是露比
I'm Ruby.
这不就是
Well...if it isn't
"不邀请人参加活动女士"吗
"Miss doesn't invite people to stuff."
也是大家熟知的"非常非常漂亮女士"
Who's also known as Miss Very, Very Pretty.
本美女不需要别人告诉我我漂亮
I don't need someone to tell me that I'm pretty.
当年我也是这么对为我写出
That's what I told Roy Orbison
《漂亮女人》的罗伊·奥比森说
when he wrote "Pretty Woman" for me.
你们俩姑娘来做什么
What do you little girls want?
我们是厄尔的朋友
We're friends of Earl.
-哪个厄尔 -那个厄尔啊
- Of Earl? - You know, Earl.
早鸟乐队那个
From The Early Birds.
就是让这酒吧蓬荜生辉的那个厄尔
You know, the guy who put this club on the map.
那个厄尔啊
Oh, that Earl!
他是个废柴渣男
He's a bum!
八婆 你最好掂掂自己斤两
Girl, you better check yourself!
不许有任何人说我的厄尔坏话
No one says anything bad about my Earl.
你的厄尔 我的确不想因为
Your Ear--Well, I prefer not to go to jail
杀了厄尔的女友而坐牢 但是...
for murdering Earl's girlfriend, but...
不想的欲望也没那么强烈
it's not that strong a preference.
来 帮我拿着耳环
Here, hold my hoops!
不是不是不是
Oh, no, no, no, no.
麦克斯不是厄尔的女朋友
Max isn't Earl's girlfriend.
厄尔对他而言更像是个父亲形象
He's more like a father-figure to her.
是太爷爷形象吧
More like a great-grandfather figure!
他两者皆是 拿着我耳环
He's both! Hold my hoops!
大家冷静 休息几个节拍[挨打]
Everybody calm down, take a beat.
我是指爵士风节拍
A jazzy beat, of course.
我只有两个问题问你
I only have two questions for you--
她是在不爽什么
Why is she so upset?
还有爵士风节拍是什么鬼
And what the hell is a jazzy beat?
我不爽
I'm upset
是因为这酒吧也有厄尔的一份力
because I know Earl helped build this club,
但周年演出却不受邀请
and he wasn't invited to play your anniversary show.
没错 因为他是个废柴渣男
That's right-- 'cause he's a bum!
再帮我拿着耳环
Hold my hoops again!
那个废柴又脚踏两条船的音乐天才
That no-good, two-timin' musical genius
在我死前绝对别想踏进我酒吧一步
will never set foot in my club while I'm alive.
来 拿着我耳环
Here, hold my hoops
我把脚踝上的枪解下来
while I unstrap the pistol on my shoe.
露比 拜托了 你就不能让他表演吗
Ruby, come on, can't you just let him play?
他现在就只是一个餐厅收银员罢了
I mean, he's just a cashier at a diner now.
你刚才说他什么
What'd you just call him?
厄尔绝对不止是个收银员
Earl is more than just a cashier.
收银只是工作 不是他的本质
That is his job, not what he is.
你好大的狗胆
How dare you!
对啊 她哪来的胆子
Yeah, how dare she!
拿着我的耳环
Hold my hoops!
都收了神通吧 我错了
Hold your hoops! I'm sorry.
他不是收银员 他是音乐天才
He's not a cashier. He's a musical genius.
靠
Damn it.
真不敢相信那个厄尔会沦落到
I can't believe that Earl would end up
在餐厅里做没有前途的收银员
in a dead-end job as a cashier in a diner.
也不见得就真的没前途啊
Well, I mean, it doesn't have to be a dead-end.
他也是随时有可能
He could get out anytime--
跟餐厅里的其他人一起振翅高飞
him and the other people that work there.
好啦 他可以来表演
All right, he can come.
但必须确定他会来 而且保持清醒
But just make sure he shows up and he is sober.
这家伙只有两个模式
That man only has two settings--
"嗨到翻"与"干到翻"
"High off his ass" or "not in the room."
他会来的
He'll be here.
我不知道哪个耳环是谁的了
Okay, I don't know whose hoops are whose.
我们有点陷入"环环相扣"的情况了
We got a real "whose hoops" over here.
厄尔 这很兴奋吧
Isn't that exciting, Earl?
你要在酒吧演出
You're playing at the club!
我要把这个称为"风云再起"
I'm gonna go ahead and call it a comeback.
然后我要去找一件可以"穿完再退"的衣服
And then I'm gonna go find an outfit that I can take back.
厄尔 明显我当你的女伴
So, Earl, obviously, I'll be your date,
还有很明显 我们都会假装不认识卡洛琳
and obviously, we'll pretend that we don't know Caroline.
我真不敢相信你们俩去找了露比
I can't believe that you girls went to see Ruby
回来时耳环和头发还能安然无恙
and came back with your hoops and hair.
但有一个问题
But there's one problem:
我没有萨克斯风了
I no longer own a saxophone.
你怎么可能会没有萨克斯风呢
How can you not own a saxophone?
就像是我怎么可能会没有大奶
That's like me not owning muh jugs.
我需要钱卖掉了
I sold it 'cause I needed the money.
我最近刚戒掉海洛因
I had just kicked heroin,
所以花钱买了很多可卡因
and I was buying a lotta cocaine.
还是谢谢你们 如果这事成了一定很赞
But thanks, girls. It would have been really nice.
厄尔 这太遗憾了
Aw, Earl, that's too bad.
我本来很兴奋看这场演出呢
I was really excited to see the show.
可能我去露比酒吧时 染上了爵士兴头[虫]
I think when we went to Ruby's, I caught the jazz bug.
在我那个年代 染上"爵士虫"就得梅毒了
In my day, when you caught the jazz bug, you had syphilis.
很明显 我们得给厄尔整把萨克斯风来
Obviously, we have to get Earl a saxophone
好让他能去演出
so he can play in the show.
麦克斯 如果你对我们生活也如此上心
Max, if you put this much effort into our life,
我们早就不用上《从未闯出名堂》杂志封面
we'd be off the cover of "Never Made It" magazine.
我们买不起乐器
We can't afford a musical instrument.
放心我 这世上我最会找的东西
Trust me, if there's anything I know how to find,
就是便宜萨克斯风[性爱]
it's cheap sax.
厄尔 重回你震撼全场的地方
So, Earl, you're back in your old stomping grounds.
感觉如何
How's it feel?
是不是勾起很多过往的回忆呀
Should bring back a lotta memories, huh?
那当然
It sure should!
那是我的妞
There's my girl!
我和她以前可多话聊了
She and I used to have a lot of great talks.
厄尔 你跟第一爵士夫人艾拉合作过吗
Earl, you played with Ella Fitzgerald?
有可能
It's possible.
不然我就是对着她的照片自说自话
Or else I talked to that picture.
我当时嗑药可猛了
I did a lot of drugs.
每当我想到艾拉 我就想
Whenever I think of Ella, I just want to
学她那首《月儿高高》里的拟声吟唱
♪ Scooby-doo-bop-bop, squiddly dop-dop-bah ♪
你再这样
Do that again,
我就打得你"脑儿爆爆"
and I'm gonna squiddly-da-bop you in the head.
我必须承认 上台演奏让我兴奋
I gotta admit, I'm excited to play.
我已经运起我的表演功力
I got my mojo working
以及起搏器的定速控制开关
and my pacemaker on cruise control.
感谢为我费心 姑娘们
I appreciate all the trouble, girls.
等你成功了 别忘了我们就行
Just don't forget us when you make it big.
等我们成功了 也不会忘了你的
And we won't forget you when we make it big.
哎哟哟
Well, well, well.
厄尔带着两个18岁的小白妞
Earl with a couple of 18-year-old white girls.
60年代的场景再度重演
It's the '60s all over again.
如果真是60年代
If it was the '60s,
咱俩现在已经在衣帽间
you and I would be in the coat closet
扭动优雅身躯 做起不雅之事
gettin' on the good foot doin' the bad thing.
你跟以前一样美 露比
You look beautiful as ever, Ruby.
厄尔
Well, Earl,
不得不说 你看起来...
I must say, you look...
更有智慧 出类拔萃
Wiser? Distinguished?
如陈年佳酿那般香醇
Mature like a fine wine.
我本想说 毒粉味没那么重
I was gonna say less on heroin.
我已经30年没沾过海洛因了
I haven't done smack in 30 years.
我连"孩落婴"麦片都不吃了
I even quit Honey Smacks
因为我怕它会勾起我的毒虫
'cause I thought it might tempt me.
露比 告诉你一声
Ruby, just putting it out there--
如果你需要人热场子
if you need someone to warm up the crowd,
我可是在高中时参加过爵士合唱团
I was in my high school's jazz choir.
我会唱《上帝保佑这孩子》
I sang "God Bless the Child."
上帝真该保佑
Well, God bless the children
听你唱歌的这些孩子
that had to listen to that.
今晚一定会非常有意思 厄尔
Well, it's gonna be very interesting, Earl.
我从来没见过你清醒时演出
I don't think I ever remember you playing sober.
你过去总说 嗨了之后你来劲儿
You always said the junk gave you the funk.
是吗
I did?
这话真妙
Well, that was clever.
那你知道什么很不妙吗
You know what wasn't clever?
把内裤忘在我妹妹的早餐桌上
Leaving your underpants on my sister's breakfast table.
总之 祝好运[断了一条腿]
Anyway, break a leg.
或伤了一颗心
Or...A heart.
反正你最擅长了
You're good at that.
我擅长跟你做很多事情 露比
I was good at a lot of things with you, Ruby.
姑娘们 我刚意识到
Girls, I just realized...
我从未清醒演出过
I never played straight.
失陪了 两位
Excuse me, ladies.
我得去洗手间清醒一下
I have to freshen up in the men's room.
你也觉得"清醒一下"不是...
You don't think "freshen up" means...
咱俩认为的那个意思吧
what I think we both think it means.
不会啦 厄尔都戒毒30年了
No. Earl's been clean for 30 years.
再说了 谁会去以前吸毒的那家爵士酒吧的
Plus, you don't just go into the bathroom of a jazz club
那间洗手间找毒吸啊
where you did heroin to find heroin.
我去偷看一下
I'll just go take a peek.
厄尔还在洗手间
Earl's still in the bathroom.
你知道什么不在洗手间吗
You know what's not in the bathroom?
隔间的门
Doors on the stalls.
糟糕 我都忘了我有邀请客人
Damn it! I forgot I invited people.
姑娘们 拜托
Hey, girls, come on.
承认吧 没人喜欢爵士 对吧
Admit it-- everyone hates jazz, right?
我就喜欢啊
Well, I love it.
瞧 爵士果然是最糟的
See? It's the worst!
我喜欢去市中心[口交]
I like going downtown.
这点不说你也知道吧
I don't have to tell you that.
阿憨呢
Where's Han?
他就站在我底下 对吗
He's standing right under me, isn't me?
一杯喝的要15块
Ooh! $15 a drink.
在新泽西一晚才花这么多
That's your whole night in Secaucus!
阿憨 我不能同时忍受
Han, I can't take shots and jazz
打针 爵士乐还有你的抠门
and your personality at the same time.
苏菲 放轻松 没事的
Sophie, relax. It'll be fine.
我先请你喝一杯吧
I'll buy you a drink first.
我拿信用卡 你先帮我拿着注射器
Hold my syringe while I get my credit card.
你是谁 我妈吗
Who are you, my mom?
厄尔 你还好吗
Oh, Earl, how you doing?
麦克斯 你真贴心
Max, that's real sweet of you
还帮我搞了点毒品 但我还是算了吧
to score some dope for me, but I'm gonna pass.
不 这是苏菲的生育药
No. These are Sophie's fertility drugs.
这会让你长出大胸
All this'll give you is great breasts.
还是算了 如果我有大胸
Still no. If I had great breasts,
那我肯定在床上不愿下来
I'd never get out of bed.
晚上好 我是露比
Good evening. My name is Ruby.
以防大家忘记
And in case you forget that,
所以我用霓虹灯写在每个角落
it's written in neon all over the place.
-你准备好了吗 -好了 准备走了
- You ready? - Yep. Ready to leave.
-什么 -你也听露比说了
- What? - You heard Ruby.
我以前都是嗨了才能吹
I've never played not high,
但我现在不打算嗨
and I'm not about to try it now.
我知道大家今晚是为了早鸟乐队而来的
Now, I know you're all here for The Early Birds tonight,
所以大家准备好 快把妹妹藏好
so hang onto your hats and hide your sisters.
跟我一起欢迎他回到舞台
And help me welcome back to the stage
有请早鸟乐队的灵魂 厄尔
The Early Birds, featuring Earl!
厄尔
Earl!
我还在这里吗
Oh, a-am I still here?
在我脑中 我已经在十万八千里外
In my mind, I was running so fast.
厄尔 我们都在等你呢
Earl...we're waiting for you.
他磨磨唧唧 好像舞台
He's acting like the stage
想跟他确立一夫一妻制的关系似的
wants him to commit to a monogamous relationship.
你们懂我的意思吧 女士们
You know what I'm talkin' about, right, ladies?
爵士太有趣了
Yeah, jazz is funny!
你们知道该怎么做 先即兴伴奏吧
Boys, y'all know the drill. Vamp! Vamp, boys, vamp.
你得上去 帮我们拖延时间
You gotta go up and buy us some time
我去劝厄尔上台
so I can convince Earl to get up there.
麦克斯 我不知道我能不能做到
Max, I don't know if I could do that.
我该上去唱《上帝保佑这孩子》
Should I go with "God Bless the Child"
还是《女士唱起布鲁斯》
or "Lady Sings the Blues"?
不要再往你身上加白东西了
Quit adding white things to you.
你已经是这里最白[痴]的人了
You're already the whitest person here.
快去吧
Just go.
各位狂热粉们大家好啊
Hey, there, you crazy cats.
厄尔即将登台
Earl will be out in a hot second.
大家好咩
How y'all doin'?
一呀 二呀 三呀
And-a one, and-a two, and-a three...
这里有三杯马丁尼酒
martinis over on this table!
你们知道那种明明是别人在说蠢话
You know when someone else says something stupid,
自己却尴尬癌发作的感觉吗
but you're embarrassed?
厄尔 我以为这会让你开心
Earl, I thought this would make you happy,
但如果你不想演奏 那我们可以走
but if you don't wanna play, we can just go.
-那我们走吧 -靠 厄尔
- Then let's just go. - Damn it, Earl!
音乐跟上来 小伙子们
Follow along, boys.
保持活泼轻快
Just keep it bright and breezy,
弹奏《上帝保佑这孩子》
and "God Bless the Child."
你在逗我玩吗
Is this a joke?
不来一针毒品我是撑不过去这关了
I'm gonna have to shoot up myself to get through this.
夏日深夜 蟋蟀南下
Sometimes when the crickets start chirpin' down South
开始鸣叫
late on a summer's night...
你他妈在逗我玩吗
Seriously-- is this a joke?
等我唱到正题就行了
I just have to break into this song.
老天
Oh, lord.
谁往我心上用力开一枪吧
Somebody shoot me!
麦克斯 结果最后发现
You know what, Max, it turns out
我不需要毒品也能上台
I don't need junk to get up there.
只要卡洛琳开口唱歌就行
I just needed Caroline to start singing.
起飞吧 鸟儿们
Let's fly, Birds.
A-five, six, seven, eight.
谢谢你热场 亲爱的
Thanks for warming them up, darling.
厄尔 我可以留下来唱歌
On, Earl, I can stay and sing--
心领了
We good.
掌声欢送 卡洛琳·钱宁
Caroline Channing, folks.
各位 谢谢你们今晚来这里
Everybody, thank you all for coming out tonight.
Okay, a-one, two, three...
这个收银员真酷
That is one cool cashier.
他真是宝刀未老
He's still got it!
没错
Yes, he does.
我只知道如果那个白妞再开口唱歌
All I know is if that white girl had started singin',
你就得帮我拿着耳环了
you were gonna have to hold my hoops!
厄尔一路都在打瞌睡
Wow, Earl's been napping pretty much this whole time.
今晚对他很重要啊
It was a big night for him.
他重振雄风[骑上马背]
He got back on the horse
却没有碰毒[马]一丝
without getting back on the horse.
但我确定露比有"感受"到他的"雄风"
But I'm pretty sure he got back on Ruby.
我知道他重新上了她
I know he got back on her,
因为我得帮她拿耳环
'cause I had to hold her hoops.
虽然我很不想这么说
I hate to say this,
但我有点嫉妒厄尔
but I'm a little jealous of Earl.
他能有机会再次做自己擅长的事
He got a chance to do what he's best at again.
我开始觉得自己再也没有这种机会了
I'm beginning to think I may never get that chance.
你之前不还怀抱希望吗
Aw, were you holding on to hope?
打住 你还有时间 厄尔都80岁了
Stop. You have time. Earl's 80.
而你现在...才50岁 对吧
You're only, what, like 50 now?
麦克斯 人家今晚真的很想唱歌嘛
Max, I really wanted to sing tonight.
好吧
Fine.
厄尔 醒醒
Earl, wake up.
糟糕
Damn it.
我又住在地铁里了吗
Have I been living on the subway again?
不是 卡洛琳需要你伴奏
No. Caroline needs you to play.
我不觉得我能在地铁上唱歌
Oh, I don't think I could sing on the subway.
《上帝保佑这孩子》 G调
"God Bless the Child" in a G.
卡洛琳 你不会真的要唱布鲁斯吧
Caroline, you're not really gonna sing the blues.
那音乐是在唱受苦受难
I mean, that music's about suffering,
倾诉痛失一切的苦闷
the pain of losing everything.
像你这样的女孩又怎么会懂呢
How would a girl like you know about that?
我痛失50亿美元身家
I lost $5 billion.
你刚说G调是吧
Key of G, you said.
不好意思
'Scuse me--
这位姑娘要为大家唱一曲
this girl's going to sing for you right now.
我们不要钱 所以千万别扔东西
We don't want money, so don't throw a thing.
各位请听
So everybody listen up.
你就算了 先生
Not you, sir.
我知道你忙着自慰
I know you're busy masturbating.
准备好了吗
Ready?
♪ 应该得到应得的 ♪
♪ Them's that got shall have ♪
很好
Yeah.
♪ 不该失去拥有的 ♪
♪ Them's that's not shall lose ♪
-♪ 《圣经》曾说 ♪ -很好
- ♪ So the bible said ♪ - Yeah!
♪ 现在仍是这么说 ♪
♪ And it still is news ♪
♪ 妈妈可能有 ♪
♪ Mama may have ♪
♪ 爸爸可能有 ♪
♪ Papa may have ♪
♪ 但上帝保佑这孩子 ♪
♪ But God bless the child ♪
♪ 这个靠自己的孩子 ♪
♪ That's got his own ♪
太好了
Yeah...
好了 各位开始扔钱吧
All right, everybody start throwing some money.
我之前没想到她能唱这么好
I didn't think she was gonna be that good.